Break UAV Gloo
Still people right in front of us
Is it 4-4 right?
Nah, it’s not 4-4.
I’ll go the left.
One left isolated.
Bro, let me heal up real quick!
I’m pushing left now!
Yo, they’re going through the electric pole!
Pressure the electric tower!
Come over here.
Anyone at the electric tower?
Two players.
Wait, let me nade first.
Take it slow, don’t push yet.
Alright, okay.
Just throw grenade
Push him, NLUANN!
I’ll break UAV gloo
Zone is coming our side
MinkCuog, you got this!
UAV heal and UAV gloo here.
TheGod, any more UAV heal?
UAV heal is here.
Both UAV heal and gloo, too!
Yo, right side!
Check the right again!
That hurts!
Is it 4-4 or something?
Right side is weak!
1 weak
He’s already using to fight me
Still 4-4, guys!
Pick 1!
Let’s go, MinhCuog!
Pick 2!
Nice!
Only two left, NLUANN!
Yo, save me! I’m down behind the gloo wall, MinkCuog!
Drop gloo wall, MinhCuog!
Got it!
Shoot the close one, guys! Focus the close one!
Do you have Oscar? Oscar, go for it!!!
Oscar, MinkCuog!
Wait!
This pick!
Good, done!
Pick 3!
Last guy!
Where’s the last one?
Is he is up or something?
He’s near by me, low HP!
SO WHATTT?!
Nice!
LET’S GOOOO!
Genius????
You are genius, MinkCuog?